

Eneas Baroni

Córdoba, Argentina. linkedin.com/in/eneasbaroni/ github.com/eneasbaroni eneasbaroni@gmail.com +54 (351) 2110423

ABOUT ME

Full Stack Developer (MERN stack) with a strong background in Architecture and Graphic Design passionate about creating immersive and visually striking digital experiences.

+6 years of experience as a Project Manager. Developing, managing, and overseeing large-scale projects.

Possessing a great ability to merge technology with art and aesthetics, creating digital solutions that are not only functional but also true works of art.

I am constantly seeking challenges that push the limits of my knowledge and creativity.

EXPERIENCE

TUTOR OF BACKEND at CODERHOUSE

2023-Present

RESPONSIBILITIES

- Accompany the learning of the students during the course.
- Correct practical works.
- Teach of complementary classes.

FULL STACK DEVELOPER Freelance

2021-Present

RESPONSIBILITIES

- Diseño web.
- Web development. Frontend and Backend

Technologies Used: HTML, CSS, SASS, JAVASCRIPT, REACT JS, NEXT JS, ANGULAR JS, ASTRO, FIREBASE, NODE JS, EXPRESS, BOOTSTRAP, TAILWIND.

PROJECT MANAGER at SIMSA Clima

2016-Present

RESPONSIBILITIES

- Design of thermomechanical engineering projects. Establishing their requirements
- Material Take Off, and budget.
- Project management and development. Defining the necessary resources, coordinating and/or supervising the different teams involved in each project.

Technologies Used: Autocad - Revit - Excel - Thermomechanical design software (Various)

KEY ACCOMPLISHMENTS

- Optimization of development times through template automation
- Optimization of design times through the implementation of new technologies and modalities of use.

PROJECT DESIGNER at Tesicom/Ingeniería Eléctrica SRL

2012-2016

RESPONSIBILITIES

- Design of electrical engineering projects, development of preliminary projects and computation of materials required for the works.
- Project development. Defining the necessary resources and developing technical graphics at different levels of detail.
- Design of corporate graphics.

Technologies Used: Autocad - Revit - Excel - Illustrator - Photoshop

SKILLS

Soft skills

Adaptability - Agile Principles - Fast Learning - Planning - Problem Solving - Project Management - Team Player

Hard skills

Adobe Illustrator - Adobe Photoshop - Angular - Astro - Autocad - Bootstrap - Express - HTML / CSS - JavaScript - NextJS - NodeJS Python - ReactJS - Tailwind - Object-Oriented Programming (OOP) - Scrum - Sketchup - SQL

EDUCATION

PYTHON

CERTIFICATE COURSE Coderhouse Institute 2022-2022

FULL STACK DEVELOPMENT (MERN)

CERTIFICATE COURSE Coderhouse Institute 2021-2022

FULL STACK DEVELOPMENT (MERN)

CERTIFICATE COURSE

Argentina Programa - Government of the Nation 2021-2023

ARCHITECT

UNIVERSITY DEGREE Facultad de Arquitectura Urbanismo y Diseño - UNC 2008-2018

GRAPHIC DESIGN - Level 1 and 2

CERTIFICATE COURSE Aguas de la Cañada - Escuela de Diseño 2014-2015

LANGUAGES

SPANISH: Native

ENGLISH: Intermediate B1-B2